University Library Records, 1979-2003
The University Library
University Library Records,
1979-2003
UA 21
University of California, Santa Cruz
3 linear ft.
University of California, Santa Cruz. University Library. Special Collections and Archives Santa Cruz, California 95064
Includes documents and records relating to the administration of the University Library
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Transferred in 2003.
Scope and Contents Note
Includes documents and records relating to the administration of the University Library.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
University of California, Santa Cruz--Archives
Other Index Terms Related to this Collection
University of California, Santa Cruz. University Library; University of California, Santa Cruz. Science Library; University of California, Santa Cruz. McHenry Library
Collection Contents
- Restricted material, 1990, 9 folders
  This series contains restricted material from the University Library.
  - RESTRICTED FILES (Box-folder 1:1-9)
- Reports and Statistics, 1979-2003, 5 half cartons
  This series contains reports and monthly statistics of the University Library.
  - LMG - Library Management Group Reports (Box-folder 2:6, 3:1-3)
    - July 1979-December 1981 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 2:2)
    - 1983-84 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - 1985-87 (Box-folder 2:4)
    - 1988-1990 (Box-folder 2:5)
    - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 2:6)
    - 1993-1995 (Box-folder 3:1)
    - 1996-1998 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - 1999-2002 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Automation Committee [formerly Database Committee] (Box-folder 3:4-5)
    - Oct 1987-Mar 1992 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Oct 1986-Jun 1987 (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Database Committee, Oct 1979-Jun 1980 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Section Reports Monthly Statistics (Box-folder 3:7 - 5:5)
    - 1984-1985 (Box-folder 4:1)
    - Jul 1985 - Jun 1986 (Box-folder 4:2)
    - Jul 1986 - Jun 1987 (Box-folder 4:3)
    - Jul 1987 - Jun 1988 (Box-folder 4:4)
    - Jul 1988 - Jun 1989 (Box-folder 4:5)
    - Jul 1989 - Jun 1990 (Box-folder 4:6)
    - Jul 1990 - Jun 1991 (Box-folder 5:1)
    - Jul 1991 - Jun 1992 (Box-folder 5:2)
    - Jul 1992 - Jun 1993 (Box-folder 5:3)
    - Jul 1993 - Jun 1994 (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Jul 1994 - Jun 1995 (Box-folder 5:5)
    - Jul 1995 - Jun 1996 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Jul 1996 - Jun 1998 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Jul 1998 - Jun 2001 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Jul 2001 - Mar 2003 (Box-folder 3:10)
- Science Library Building Committee, 1984-1987, 2 half cartons
  This series contains material about the construction of the Science Library.
  - Science Library Building Committee (Box-folder 5:6 - 6:13)
    - Circulation Reference (Box-folder 5:6)
    - Construction Meetings (Box-folder 5:7)
    - Correspondence Publicity (Box-folder 5:8)
    - Awards Photos (Box-folder 6:1)
    - Dedication, Millionth volume, etc. event (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Cowell Grant (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Meeting Notes (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Building Planning - Pre-building committee (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Site dedication (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Preliminary Design Submittal - Outline Specs (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Final EIR, 10/1987 (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Detailed Project Program, DPP Revised, 7/1987 (Box-folder 6:9)
    - PPG, revised (Box-folder 6:10-11)
      - 10/1985 (Box-folder 6:10)
      - 9/1986 (Box-folder 6:11)
    - PPG addendums (Box-folder 6:12-13)
      - 8/1987 (Box-folder 6:12)
      - 9/1987 (Box-folder 6:13)